大家好，美丽的人们，欢迎回来。
Hello you beautiful people and welcome back.
因此，让我们继续并使我们的工作与find命令完全极端。
So let's go ahead and make our work with the find command totally extreme.
好的。
OK.
因此，让我们继续在桌面上创建一个名为Hystack的文件夹。
So let's just go ahead and create a folder on our desktop called haystack.
好的。
OK.
所以这就是它出现的原因。
So there it is that appeared.
我们在这里能做的就是制作500个文件夹。
And what we can do in here is we're going to make five hundred folders.
现在我想看看你能不能记住怎么做，如果你能记住如何使用花括号扩展的话
Now I want to see if you can remember how to do this if you can remember how to use brace expansion
要创建500个称为文件夹的文件夹，您知道的，从一个文件夹一直到三个文件夹，直到
to create 500 folders that are called you know folder one folder to folder three all the way up until
文件夹。
folder.
五百元。
Five hundred.
所以现在就去上传一段视频吧。
So go ahead and post a video now.
尝试使用大括号扩展使文件夹1到干草堆文件夹内的文件夹500，然后来
Try to use brace expansion to make folder one to folder 500 inside of the haystack folder and then come
回来看看你们进展如何
back to see how you got on
如果你能上车的话。
Had you get on.
你成功了吗。
Did you manage it.
如果有这么好的记忆力的话。
If so great memory.
如果没有，别担心。
If not don't worry.
已经有一段时间了。
It's been awhile.
让我们实际尝试一下，看看我们是否可以正确执行此操作，我们要做的是创建目录
Let's actually try and see if we can do this right where we're going to do is we want to make directory
干草堆劈开文件夹一点500。
haystack slash folder one dot dot 500.
好的。
OK.
这就是说，将文件夹1到500放在草垛文件夹内。
So this is saying make folder 1 to 500 inside the haystack folder.
当我按Enter键，我们在干草堆中查找时，我们在那里有100个文件夹，我可能应该更换一下
When I press enter and we look in haystack we've got 100 folders in there and I probably should change
布局。
the layout.
我们走吧。
There we go.
文件夹1 2文件夹500试图用鼠标结束，指向并单击它会让你
Folder one 2 folder 500 tried to end up with your mouse and pointing and clicking it will take you for
永远不会。
ever.
所以我们走吧。
So there we go.
我们现在已经做到了，在每个文件夹中，我们需要创建100个文件，500个文件夹中的100个文件。
We've done that now in each of those folders we need to make 100 files a hundred files in 500 folders.
没错。
That's right.
而且这实际上一点也不难做到。
And it's actually not difficult to do at all.
挑战号码，看看您是否还记得如何将触摸命令与花括号展开一起使用
So Challenge number to see if you can remember how to use the touch command with brace expansion to
创建100个称为文件、一个文件到三个文件的文件，直到在每个文件中创建100个文件
create 100 files called file one file to file three all the way until file one hundred in each of the
五百个文件夹。
five hundred folders.
好的，那就继续吧，试一试。
OK so go ahead and give that a go.
然后回来看看你做得怎么样。
And then come back to see how you did.
好的，你怎么做到的。
All right how do you do that.
我更努力一点。
I was a bit harder.
希望你拿到了。
Hopefully you got it.
如果没有，别担心。
If not don't worry.
这就是我做这件事的方式。
This is how I've gone about doing it.
好的。
OK.
所以我会使用touch命令，因为这是我们用来创建文件的。
So I'd use the touch command because that's what we use to create files.
我会说好的，在干草堆文件夹里，从1到500，我要你把文件变成1到100。
And I'd say OK in haystack folder in folder one to five hundred I want you to make file 1 to 100.
好的，如果我继续这样做，我们会看到的。
OK so if I go ahead and do that we shall see that.
在每个文件夹中，我们现在应该有100个文件，所以现在还有一个文件夹用于
Inside each of these folders now we should have 100 files so there be others folder one now has for
1到100。
1 to 100.
如果我选择另一个文件夹，则文件夹26代表1到100，以此类推，如果我们一直往下走到文件夹402
If I pick another one have folder 26 for one to 100 and so on if we go all the way down to folder 402
它有自己的100个文件。
that's got its own 100 files.
所以你现在可以真正开始看到，当你有了所有这些不同的部件时，外壳是多么强大
So you can really start seeing now how powerful the shell is when you've got all these different pieces
你们可以一起使用。
that you can use together.
好的。
OK.
现在我们所做的是在这100个文件中的每个文件中创建一个名为haystack 500个文件夹的文件夹。
Now what we've done is we've made a folder called haystack 500 folders in each of those 100 files.
好的。
OK.
如果我的数学没问题的话，大概有50000个文件。
So about 50000 files if my math is all right.
所以现在我们要做的是，我要在这里输入一些东西，这是一个，不用担心
So now what we're going to do is I'm going to just type something here it's a it don't worry about how
它可以工作，但我将在此处键入一些代码，这些代码将在其中一个运行中创建
it works but I'm going to type a bit a bit of code here that's going to create in one of the run in
其中一个文件夹。
one of the folders.
好的。
OK.
从1到500的其中一个文件夹我们要做的是找到一个我们要访问的文件
One of the folders from one to 500 what we're going to do is we're going to find a file that we're going
制作一个名为Neidl Dr.XTi的文件。
to make a file called Neidl Dr. XTi.
好的。
OK.
这就是说触摸随机文件夹中的内容。
So what this is saying is touch inside a random folder.
它可以是文件夹1到500文件中的任意随机数，称为针60。
It can be folder 1 to 500 any random number in the file called needle that 60.
所以我们已经创建了一个名为针的文件，它将t放入干草堆中的某个位置，但我们不知道它在哪里
So we've created a file called needle that takes t in somewhere in the haystack but we don't know where
现在我们的工作是使用find命令来找到它。
and it's our job now to use the find command in order to find it.
好的。
OK.
那么我们怎么才能找到针呢。
So how can we find the needle.
让我们仔细考虑一下，清除屏幕并将其最大化。
Let's have a think through this clear the screen and maximize it.
所以，让我们来看看我们将如何做到这一点。
So let's just take a look how we might do this.
所以首先我们可以使用find命令。
So first of all we can use the find command.
好的。
OK.
我们要从哪里开始，从哪里开始。
And we're going to start where are we going to start.
我们可能从干草堆文件夹开始。
We probably start with the haystack folder.
好的，我们知道它就在大海捞针里，所以我们要从这一点开始搜索。
OK we know it's in the haystack so we're going to start searching from that point.
我们知道这是一份文件，对吧。
And we know that it's a file right.
因此，我们不需要查看所有目录，但请记住，默认情况下，find命令将
So we don't need to look at all the directories but remembering that the find command will by default
列出文件和目录。
list out files and directories.
所以我们需要担心在所有的搜索和返回文件夹中进行搜索，让我们
So we need to worry about searching through all the you know searching and returning folders let's just
查找文件。
look for files.
我们知道它的名字是Nido Dottie axiUm Way。
And we know that its name is Nido Dottie axium way.
好的。
OK.
所以，如果我们这样做，看看它是否有效，它是好的，它找到了可以进入内部的针头
So if we do that and Precentor and see if it works and it has OK it's found needle that takes the inside
文件夹。
folder.
449。
Four hundred and forty nine.
太不对劲了，我们已经设法大海捞针了，但现在让我们试着把它搬开
How awesome is not right we've managed to find the needle in a haystack but now let's try and move it
到桌面上。
to the desktop.
好的。
OK.
现在我们已经得到了结果，要做到这一点，我们将使用确切的选项对其执行某些操作。
So to do that now that we've got the result we will use the exact option to execute something on it.
现在要搬东西了。
Now to move something.
请记住，您需要键入Move，而不是要移动的内容和要将其移动到的位置。
Remember you would type move than what you want to move and where you want to move it to.
记住，当然，我们必须以反斜杠、分号结尾。
And remember of course we've got to end everything with a backslash semi-colon.
这就是您和EXEC选项的方式。
This is how you and the exec option.
因此，我们要将某些内容移动到我们想要将其移动到桌面上的某个位置。
So we are going to move something to somewhere that we want to move it onto our desktop.
所以，就放一个倾斜的劈开桌面吧。
So just put a tilter slash desktop.
好的。
OK.
这就是我们的桌面。
So that is our desktop.
我们要把它搬到那里去。
That's where we're going to move it.
那我们要搬什么呢。
And what are we going to move.
那份文件。
Well that file.
所以我们放了一组方形的弯曲括号，它对一个文件的作用与对100000个文件的作用相同。
So we put a square set of squiggly brackets and it works the same for one file as it would for 100000.
所以，如果我们继续这样做，我们按回车键，祈祷吧。
So fingers crossed if we go ahead and do that we press enter.
现在，如果我关闭终端，在我们的桌面上看一看，我们实际上已经做到了，我们成功地做到了
And now if I just close the terminal and have a look on our desktop we've actually done it we've managed
要从可能有50000个文件堆积如山中的某个位置开始进行针式DirectX测试，请执行以下操作
to move needle directx t all the way from somewhere inside that haystack of potentially 50000 files
找到它并将其移动到我们的桌面上，这就是您过去学到的东西有多棒
find it and move it to move it to our desktop so that's just how awesome what you've learnt in the past
很少有视频可以做到这一点。
few videos can be.
因此，您在过去的几个视频中看到的是，find命令完全是一个野兽命令。
So what you've seen in the past few videos is that the find command is a total beast of a command.
你用它看到了太多太多的东西。
You've seen so many so very many things with it.
但主要的关键点，我只想做一个简短的总结。
But the main key point I'm just going to go through in a quick summary.
好的，这样就可以使用FINE命令来执行复杂的搜索任务。
OK so the fine command can be used to execute sophisticated search tasks.
您还可以看到如何使用LOCATE命令，这对于快速使用非常有用
You also see how you've seen how to use the locate command and that's very good for just quick quick
就像你知道的搜索一样。
like you know searches.
但是，如果您想做一些非常复杂的事情，那么find命令是您想要使用的。
But if you want to do something very sophisticated find command is what you're going to want to use.
首先，它不使用数据库，而LOCATE命令的FINE命令直接工作
First of all it doesn't use a database whereas the locate commando's the fine command works directly
在您的文件系统上，这意味着它总是正确的，但是可能会稍微慢一些。
on your file system which means that it's always going to be correct but it might be slightly slower.
所以这只是一件需要牢记在心的事情。
So that's just something to bear in mind.
find命令允许您构建搜索查询，您可以在其中按文件名进行搜索
And the find command allows you to build up search queries where you can search by the name of the file
你要找的东西的类型、大小等等。
the type of the thing that you're searching for the size and so much more.
好的，您可以在手册页中看到这些示例，只需键入man，然后查找，您就可以阅读了
OK you can see examples of those in the man page just type man then find and you'll be able to read
Find命令的手册页。
the manual page for the find command.
它能做的事情实在太多了。
There's just so much that it can do.
好的。
OK.
一旦获得了这个大的结果列表，您就可以使用exec选项来执行另一个命令
And once you've got this big list of results you can use the exec option to execute another command
这些结果中的每一个。
on each of those results.
只要记住以反斜杠结束，而不是分号。
Just remember to end that with the backslash than a semi-colon.
如果您正在处理少量文件，并且您正在做一些可能具有破坏性的事情
And if you're working with a small number of files and you're doing something potentially destructive
比如删除或移除或者类似的东西，或者移动文件，那么你就知道了，可以使用OK选项来代替。
like deleting or removing or something like that or moving files then you know use the OK option instead.
因为然后它会提示你说这个可以吗，或者这个可以吗，或者这个可以吗，你必须
Because then it will prompt you to say is this one OK or is this OK or is this OK and you've got to
每次都要授权。
authorize it every time.
因为这也是需要牢记的事情。
Because that's something to bear in mind as well.
现在，在您从过去几年中了解到Find命令之后，您可以
Now after what you've learned from the last few years about the find command everything else that you
在接下来的几个视频中可以学到的似乎真的是轻而易举的事。
can learn in the next few videos is going to seem really like a breeze.
好的，在下一个视频中，我将向您展示如何在命令行上打开文件，并阅读
OK so in the next video I'm going to be showing you how to open files on the command line and read what's
在他们体内。
inside them.
还开了很多小猫笑话。
And also be making plenty of kitten jokes.
所以对于所有这些好东西。
So for all that good stuff.
我将在下一个视频中见到你。
I'll see you in the next video.